[
  {
    "type": "intro",
    "pretext": "You’ve learned that the small “や,” “ゆ,” and “よ” can also be applied to hiragana characters modified with dakuten (゛) and handakuten (゜). Time for you to take a short quiz! But before that, let’s review:"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "G and J",
    "options": [
      "Gya – ぎゃ",
      "Gyu – ぎゅ",
      "Gyo – ぎょ",
      "Jya – じゃ",
      "Jyu – じゅ",
      "Jyo – じょ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "B and P",
    "options": [
      "Bya – びゃ",
      "Byu – びゅ",
      "Byo – びょ",
      "Pya – ぴゃ",
      "Pyu – ぴゅ",
      "Pyo – ぴょ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Pya",
    "options": ["ぴゅ", "ぴょ", "ぴゃ"],
    "answer": "ぴゃ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Pyo",
    "options": ["ぴょ", "ぴゅ", "ぴゃ"],
    "answer": "ぴょ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Gya",
    "options": ["ぎゅ", "ぎゃ", "ぎょ"],
    "answer": "ぎゃ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Byu",
    "options": ["びゃ", "びゅ", "びょ"],
    "answer": "びゅ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Gyu",
    "options": ["ぎゃ", "ぎょ", "ぎゅ"],
    "answer": "ぎゅ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Jyo",
    "options": ["じょ", "じゃ", "じゅ"],
    "answer": "じょ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Bya",
    "options": ["びゅ", "びょ", "びゃ"],
    "answer": "びゃ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Jyu",
    "options": ["じゃ", "じょ", "じゅ"],
    "answer": "じゅ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Gyo",
    "options": ["ぎょ", "ぎゃ", "ぎゅ"],
    "answer": "ぎょ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Byo",
    "options": ["びゃ", "びょ", "びゅ"],
    "answer": "びょ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Pyu",
    "options": ["ぴょ", "ぴゅ", "ぴゃ"],
    "answer": "ぴゅ"
  },
  {"type": "mc", "prompt": "Jya", "options": ["じゃ", "じょ", "じゅ"], "answer": "じゃ"}
]